export const questions = [
    {
        question: "12*12=?",
        variants: ["123", "144", "28", "238", "244"],
        rightAnswer: "144",
        id: 1,
        name: "question1"
    },
    {
        question: "10*123?",
        variants: ["1230", "1260", "1242", "1233", "1230"],
        rightAnswer: "1230",
        id: 2,
        name: "question2"
    },
    {
        question: "234/2?",
        variants: ["116", "117", "127", "118", "107"],
        rightAnswer: "117",
        id: 3,
        name: "question3"
    },
    {
        question: "1-290=??",
        variants: ["289", "-289", "-290", "-291", "AYIRIB BO'LMAYDI"],
        rightAnswer: "-289",
        id: 4,
        name: "question4"
    },
    {
        question: "23*3=??",
        variants: ["64", "66", "69", "68", "62"],
        rightAnswer: "69",
        id: 5,
        name: "question5"
    },
    {
        question: "1000-109=??",
        variants: ["989", "991", "992", "994", "981"],
        rightAnswer: "991",
        id: 6,
        name: "question6"
    },
    {
        question: "9*8=??",
        variants: ["72", "1122", "54", "64", "81"],
        rightAnswer: "72",
        id: 7,
        name: "question7"
    },
    {
        question: "3*6=??",
        variants: ["18", "15", "24", "13", "19"],
        rightAnswer: "18",
        id: 8,
        name: "question8"
    },
    {
        question: "4*504=??",
        variants: ["2016", "1233", "2123", "2160", "1200"],
        rightAnswer: "2016",
        id: 9,
        name: "question9"
    },
    {
        question: "12/24=??",
        variants: ["0.5", "2", "0.4", "1.2", "1.4"],
        rightAnswer: "0.5",
        id: 10,
        name: "question10"
    },
]